A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1965-1966
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: General Files, 1965-1966
  - Speech - 15 December 1965 1965-1966 (Box 42)
  - Speech - "What is the University of Virginia" - 4 January 1966 1965-1966 (Box 42)
  - Speech - 13 January 1966 1965-1966 (Box 42)
  - Speech - 1 March 1966 1965-1966 (Box 42)
  - State Board for Community Colleges 1965-1966 (Box 42)
  - State Board of Education 1965-1966 (Box 42)
  - State Council of Higher Education 1965-1966 (Box 42)
  - State Department of Education 1965-1966 (Box 42)
  - State Technical Services Act 1965-1966 (Box 42)
  - Special Committees 1965-1966 (Box 43)
  - State Universities Association (also see State Association of American Universities for joint account of business) 1965-1966 (Box 43)
  - Statistics 1965-1966 (Box 43)
  - Comptroller Report: Report of the Comptroller, University of Virginia1965-1966 (Box 43)
  - Student Affairs (see also Foreign Student Advisor; Fraternities; Fellowships and Scholarships) 1965-1966 (Box 43)
  - Student Aid and Placement - Committee on Student Financial Aid 1965-1966 (Box 43)
  - Student Costs 1965-1966 (Box 43)
  - Student Council 1965-1966 (Box 43)
  - Student Health Department 1965-1966 (Box 43)
  - Summer Sessions - Finals 1965-1966 1965-1966 (Box 43)
  - Summer Session - 1965 1965-1966 (Box 43)
  - "T" Miscellaneous 1965-1966 (Box 44)
  - Traffic Control 1965-1966 (Box 44)
  - "U" Miscellaneous 1965-1966 (Box 44)
  - UNESCO 1965-1966 (Box 45)
  - U. S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare 1965-1966 (Box 45)
  - U. Department of State 1965-1966 (Box 45)
  - U. S. Naval Academy 1965-1966 (Box 45)
  - University Center in Virginia 1965-1966 (Box 45)
  - University Hall (see also Field House Committee) 1965-1966 (Box 45)
  - University Houses 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - University Houses - Faulkner 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - University Houses - "Morea" 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - University Press of Virginia 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - University Printing Office 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - "V" Miscellaneous 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - Virginia College Building Authority (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - Virginia Commission on Higher Education Facilities 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - Virginia Education Association 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - Virginia Historical Society 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - Visitors - Athletics Committee 1965-1966 (Box 47)
  - Visitors - Blandy Farm 1965-1966 (Box 47)
  - Visitors - Buildings and Grounds 1965-1966 (Box 47)
  - Visitors - Committees 1965-1966 (Box 47)
  - Visitors - Committee on Administrative Organization of the University 1965-1966 (Box 47)
  - Visitors - Committee on Special Recognition 1965-1966 (Box 47)
  - Visitors - Educational Policy Committee 1965-1966 (Box 47)
  - Visitors - Executive Committee 1965-1966 (Box 47)
  - Visitors - Finance Committee 1965-1966 (Box 47)
  - Visitors - Mary Washington College Committee 1965-1966 (Box 47)
  - Visitors - Medical Committee 1965-1966 (Box 47)
  - Visitors - Docket, 8 October 1965 1965-1966 (Box 48)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 8 October 1965 1965-1966 (Box 48)
  - Visitors - Docket, 11 December 1965 1965-1966 (Box 48)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 11 December 1965 1965-1966 (Box 48)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 8 January 1966 1965-1966 (Box 48)
  - Visitors - Docket, 12 February 1966 1965-1966 (Box 49)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 12 February 1966 1965-1966 (Box 49)
  - Visitors - Docket, 26 February 1966 1965-1966 (Box 49)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 26 February 1966 1965-1966 (Box 49)
  - Visitors - Docket, 2 April 1966 1965-1966 (Box 49)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 3 June 1966 1965-1966 (Box 49)
  - Visitors - Docket, 3 June 1966 1965-1966 (Box 50)
  - Visitors - Mr. T. H. Blanton 1965-1966 (Box 50)
  - Visitors - Mr. Charles R. Fenwich 1965-1966 (Box 50)
  - Visitors - Mrs. Nathan Lantor 1965-1966 (Box 50)
  - Visitors - Gen. E. Sclater 1965-1966 (Box 50)
  - Visitors - Mr. Woodrow Wilson Wilkerson 1965-1966 (Box 50)
  - "Wa - We" Miscellaneous 1965-1966 (Box 50)
  - "Wh - Wz" Miscellaneous 1965-1966 (Box 51)
  - Walpole Society 1965-1966 (Box 51)
  - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies 1965-1966 (Box 51)
  - Water Resources (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 51)
  - Women, Dean of 1965-1966 (Box 51)
  - "S - Y - Z" Miscellaneous 1965-1966 (Box 51)
  - YMCA 1965-1966 (Box 51)
- Series II: University Committees, 1965-1966
  - AD HOC COMMITTEE - Clinical Psychology 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - AD HOC COMMITTEE - Nursing - Diploma Program 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - AD HOC COMMITTEE - Research Policies 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - AD HOC COMMITTEE - Nursing Deanship 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Administrative Committee 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Admissions Committee 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Algernon Sydney Sullivan 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Architectural Advisory 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Athletic Advisory (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Blandy Farm Advisory (see also Blandy Farm) (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Calendar and Scheduling 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Calendar of Events (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Catalogue 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Cemetery 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Chapel (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Community Colleges Advisory (see also Chancellor) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Community Colleges Building Committee (see also Chancellor) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Computer Center (see also Computer Science Center) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Danforth Fellowships (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Extension (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Fellowships 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Foreign Students (see also Foreign Student Advisor) (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Fraternities 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Fulbright Grants 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Future of the University 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Graduate 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Gwathmey Award 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Housing 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Institutional Analysis (see also Institutional Analysis, Office of) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Lecturers: Special Lectures 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Library 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Master Plan (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Medical Affairs Policy Board 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Objects of Art (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Page-Barbour and Richard Lectures 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Processions 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Public Occasions 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Radiation Safety 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Registration 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Research 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Research in the Humanities 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Rhodes Scholarships 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Scholarships, Loans, and Employment 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Scientific Research (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Space Astronomy (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Student Activities 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Student Health 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Summer Session (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Teacher Education (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Traffic Control 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Training Center for Teachers of Handicapped Children 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - University Committee on Students 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - University Communications 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - University Press (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - University Records 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - University Union (see also Newcomb Hall) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Virginia Quarterly Review Advisory (see Virginia Quarterly Review) (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Virginia Status of University Students 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Wilson Gee Institute for Research in the Social Sciences 1965-1966 (Box 52)
  - COMMITTEE - Academic Legislation 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Community Colleges 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Admissions Policy 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Alderman Library Light-Well Addition 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Advisory Committee for the Department of Aerospace Engineering and Engineering Physics 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Advisory Committee on Placement 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Alterations and Additions to Central Heating Plant 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Arboretum Advisory 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Cabell Hall Addition 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Clinch Valley College Library Building 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Chancellor for George Mason College 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Contractual Relations 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Distinguished Professor Award 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Distinguished Student Award 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Dormitory Facilities for Women Students 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Education, School of 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Education Planning for George Mason College 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Engineering and Applied Science, School of Addition 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Faculty of Arts and Sciences on Branch Colleges, Community Colleges, and Extension Work 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Faculty Club Facilities 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Garrett Hall Addition 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - George Mason Building 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - George Mason College Library Building 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Government and Foreign Affairs Chairmanship 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Advisory Committee on Graphics 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Hospital Chapel 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Institutional Analysis 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Law, School of - Library Addition 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Long Range Planning, Utilities System 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Lynchburg Branch - School of General Studies 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Madison Field Office - School of General Studies 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Memorial Gymnasium 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Monroe Hall Classroom Addition 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Organization and Functioning of Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Orientation 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Patrick Henry Administration Academic Building - General Studies 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Personnel Practices (Civil Rights) 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Physics Building 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Proposal to NASA 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Public Education (folder empty) 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Registrar, Selection of 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Religion Department Chairman 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Roanoke Center - School of General Studies 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Rotunda Renovation 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Security and General Safety 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Student Financial Aid 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Transfer Credits for the Undergraduate Schools of the University 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - University Communications 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - University Printing Office Building 1965-1966 (Box 53)
  - COMMITTEE - Women in the Dorms 1965-1966 (Box 53)